<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Decoding AI&#39;s Evolution</title>
    <link>https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Decoding AI&#39;s Evolution</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright> </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>API-LLM-Hub: Simplifying LLM-API integration for Static Pages</title>
      <link>https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/2024/api-llm-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/2024/api-llm-hub/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, fellow code enthusiasts and AI wranglers! 🖐️🤖 You know that feeling when you&amp;rsquo;re knee-deep in a project, trying to get multiple AI models to play nice in your browser? Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;ve been there. Cue the frustrated sighs, the endless searches over GitHub issues 😢, and the &amp;ldquo;why-isn&amp;rsquo;t-this-working&amp;rdquo; hair-pulling sessions.
After one too many nights wrestling with backends, CORS issues, and the general chaos of integrating various AI APIs, I decided enough was enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YC-Dendrolinguistics: Planting Linguistic Trees in the Startup Forest</title>
      <link>https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/2024/startup-linguistic-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/2024/startup-linguistic-trees/</guid>
      <description>YC-Dendrolinguistics: Planting Linguistic Trees in the Startup Forest Hey there, fellow AI adventurers and startup enthusiasts! 🌳🚀 Today, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to give you a peek into my latest passion project: YC-Dendrolinguistics. Buckle up as we embark on a journey through the linguistic forests of Y-Combinator pitches!
The Seed of an Idea Picture this: It&amp;rsquo;s 2 AM, I&amp;rsquo;m knee-deep in YC application videos, and suddenly it hits me – what if startup pitches are like trees?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Synaptic Sparks: Why I&#39;m Wiring My Thoughts into a Neural Blogosphere</title>
      <link>https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/2024/synaptic-sparks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/2024/synaptic-sparks/</guid>
      <description>Synaptic Sparks: Why I&amp;rsquo;m Wiring My Thoughts into a Neural Blogosphere Hey there, fellow AI enthusiasts and curious minds! 🧠🤖 Today, I just want to document what&amp;rsquo;s leading to this new adventure in regular blogging.
The Knowledge Synapse Picture me back in 2019, a wide-eyed novice bouncing around the vast landscape of machine learning. I was devouring every GitHub gist, Medium post, and arXiv paper I could find, growing and learning at a dizzying pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRACTURED-SORRY-Bench: Unraveling AI Safety through Decomposing Malicious Intents</title>
      <link>https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/2024/fractured-sorry-bench/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amanpriyanshu.github.io/blogs/posts/2024/fractured-sorry-bench/</guid>
      <description>FRACTURED-SORRY-Bench: When Decomposition Meets AI Safety Hello, fellow AI enthusiasts! 🤖 Today, I wanted to dive into the FRACTURED-SORRY-Bench framework and dataset we just released. Check out the dataset, website, and github for the dataset!
The FRACTURED-SORRY Saga: A Tale of Adaptation and Decomposition Picture this: you&amp;rsquo;re wandering through the lush collection of prompt-injection and llm-red-teaming papers, marveling at some of the weird and some of the crazier attack mechanisms that have been released recently.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
